22. Plastic surgery. A little nip and tuck. She's had some work done. Do you think those are real?
They're all talking about plastic, also called cosmetic surgery. This is surgery done for no medical reason, but only to make someone look better.
Plastic surgery is becoming common in wealthy countries around the world, mostly among women.
It is women, after all, who are still pushed to be beautiful above all else.
Surprisingly, plastic surgery first became common among men. After World War I, surgeons used plastic surgery to repair horrific war injuries.
Nowadays, however, plastic surgery is sold to women as a way to feel better about themselves. For some women, it works. Surgery helps them feel more confident.
Others, however, discover that their real problems are inner, not outer, and the surgeries are serious and dangerous. Surgery is painful, and recovery takes time.
It's hard to find information on how many people die from plastic surgery each year. The number is high, especially among patients who go to untrained doctors for cheap procedures.
In addition to deaths that result from surgeries, some studies show that women who get breast implants are twice as likely to commit suicide as women who don't get implants.
Plastic surgery is a miracle for people with devastating injuries. But for normal, healthy people, plastic surgery often ends up making them look just like everyone else.
Take a close look at many popular actresses. They're all starting to look alike. They have the same shape, the same eyes, the same noses, and even the same breasts.
Is that what we really want? A world where we all look the same?
It would be better to see the beauty in many different forms.